<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Honeycomb Works</string>
    <string name="start_text">Know what you want to work on? Let\'s get started.</string>
    <string name="txt">If you want to change a habit or learn something new you\'re more likely to be successful when you:</string>
    <string name="first_point">1. Write it down</string>
    <string name="second_point">2. Set time aside to work on the change you want to make</string>
    <string name="third_point">3. Identify what could stop you</string>
    <string name="fourth_point">4. Plan what you\'ll do to stay on track</string>
    <string name="message_start">Click \'Start\' and we\'ll walk you through it. We\'ll also send you reminders over the next few weeks to keep you on track</string>
    <string name="complete_time">4 min to complete</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="Q1">First name</string>
    <string name="Q2">Last name</string>
    <string name="Q3">Email*</string>
    <string name="emailString">We will only use this information to send you reminders and follow ups to see how you got on</string>
    <string name="Q4">What habit do you want to work on? Select from the drop down menu.</string>
    <string name="Q5">What situations could I try this in? What opportunities to practice do I have? This question is required.*</string>
    <!--    <string name="q5String">What is the specific thing you\'ll do differently?-->
    <!--        The exact action you will take to make a change By being as specific as-->
    <!--        possible and identifying those situations ahead of time\, you'\re more likely to commit to action</string>-->
    <string name="Q6">When am I going to work on this habit?</string>
    <string name="q6String">Set aside a date in the next week when you know you\'ll have an opportunity
        to work on it and add to your calendar to make sure you stick to your commitment</string>
    <string name="Q7">I\'ve planned what I\'m going to do and when.
        What might stop me or get in my way? These could be practical things
        (e.g important tasks) or other things (e.g. personal fears or concerns)This question is required. *</string>
    <string name="q7String">This step is really important -
        by considering the things that could stop you, you\'ll be able to come up
        with strategies to make sure they don\'t </string>
    <string name="Q8">What can I do to make sure these things don\'t stop me?
        What can I do now or what can I tell myself to make sure I go ahead?This question is required. *</string>
    <string name="q8String">People who plan how to deal with the things that could
        stop them are much more likely to stick to their commitments</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
</resources>